<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Watcha</string>
    <string name="home_text">Watcha Want to Watch Today?</string>
    <string name="kdrama1">Alchemy of Souls</string>
    <string name="kdrama2">All of Us Are Dead</string>
    <string name="kdrama3">Business Proposal</string>
    <string name="kdrama4">Crash Landing\non You</string>
    <string name="kdrama5">Descendant of\nthe Sun</string>
    <string name="kdrama6">Goblin</string>
    <string name="kdrama7">Hometown\nCha-Cha-Cha</string>
    <string name="kdrama8">Law School</string>
    <string name="kdrama9">Love Next Door</string>
    <string name="kdrama10">Moon Lovers:\nScarlet Heart\nRyeo</string>
    <string name="kdrama11">Resident Playbook</string>
    <string name="kdrama12">Sweet Home</string>
    <string name="kdrama13">Touch Your Heart</string>
    <string name="kdrama14">True Beauty</string>
    <string name="kdrama15">Twinkling\nWatermelon</string>
    <string name="kdrama16">Vincenzo</string>
    <string name="kdrama17">When Life Gives\nYou Tangerines</string>
    <string name="kdrama18">What\'s Wrong with\nSecretary Kim</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="information_button">Information</string>
    <string name="counter1">1\/3</string>
    <string name="counter2">2\/3</string>
    <string name="counter3">3\/3</string>
    <string name="logo">Watcha</string>
    <string name="kdrama1_synopsis">Set in a fictional country called Daeho, it is about the love and growth of young mages as they overcome their twisted fates due to a forbidden magic spell known as the "alchemy of souls", which allows souls to switch bodies.</string>
    <string name="kdrama2_synopsis">A high school becomes ground zero for a zombie virus outbreak. Trapped students must fight their way out or turn into one of the rabid infected.</string>
    <string name="kdrama3_synopsis">In disguise as her friend, Ha-ri shows up to a blind date to scare him away. But plans go awry when he turns out to be her CEO - and makes a proposal.</string>
    <string name="kdrama4_synopsis">The absolute top secret love story of a chaebol heiress who made an emergency landing in North Korea because of a paragliding accident and a North Korean special officer who falls in love with her and who is hiding and protecting her.</string>
    <string name="kdrama5_synopsis">This drama tells of the love story that develops between a surgeon and a special forces officer.</string>
    <string name="kdrama6_synopsis">In his quest for a bride to break his immortal curse, Dokkaebi, a 939-year-old guardian of souls, meets a grim reaper and a sprightly student with a tragic past.</string>
    <string name="kdrama7_synopsis">A big-city dentist opens up a practice in a close-knit seaside village, home to a charming jack-of-all-trades who is her polar opposite in every way.</string>
    <string name="kdrama8_synopsis">When a grim incident occurs at their prestigious school, justice through law is put to a test by a tough law professor and his ambitious students.</string>
    <string name="kdrama9_synopsis">Renowned young architect Choi Seung-hyo runs the atelier &quot;In.&quot; Bae Seok-ryu, his childhood friend, rejoins his life after quitting her corporate job, resurfacing memories he would rather forget from their peculiar childhood bond.</string>
    <string name="kdrama10_synopsis">Ha-jin travels 1000 years back in time and lands in the era of Goryeo Dynasty as a young girl named Hae-soo. She, now trapped in another body, becomes involved in a power struggle against various vicious contenders to the throne.</string>
    <string name="kdrama11_synopsis">A story that depicts the lives of people at Jongno Yulje Medical Center. The professors, ob/gyn residents, and the friendships between these people are told, including first year ob/gyn resident Oh Yi-Young.</string>
    <string name="kdrama12_synopsis">A teenage outcast is uprooted from his residence and forced to confront terrifying monsters intent on eradicating humanity. As he battles against impossible odds, he discovers the strength to fight for survival and to protect others.</string>
    <string name="kdrama13_synopsis">A romance unfolds between a lawyer and a famous actress whose life falls apart after a scandal. She pretends to be someone else to become the lawyer secretary and join a drama written by a well-known writer.</string>
    <string name="kdrama14_synopsis">After being bullied and discriminated because of her ugly looks, a high school girl transforms herself into a gorgeous "goddess" and quickly rises to fame after mastering the art of makeup via online tutorial videos.</string>
    <string name="kdrama15_synopsis">"Sparkling Watermelon" will tell the story of a boy living a double life between a model student and a band member who gets to time slip and meets his 18-year-old father. The two will build friendships there.</string>
    <string name="kdrama16_synopsis">During a visit to his motherland, a Korean-Italian Mafia lawyer gives an unrivaled conglomerate a taste of its own medicine with a side of justice.</string>
    <string name="kdrama17_synopsis">In Jeju, the story of a spirited girl and a steadfast boy blossoms into a lifelong tale of setbacks and triumphs, proving love endures across time.</string>
    <string name="kdrama18_synopsis">Follows the budding romance between a perfect but narcissistic second-generation heir and his capable assistant.</string>
</resources>